<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root><pagename>contactus.html</pagename><title>Tinker Brook Garage Ltd - Car Servicing / Repairs / MOT Testing - Accrington
</title><description>For all your quality car and small van repairs and services come along to Tinker Brook Garage Ltd situated in the heart of Accrington.
</description><keywords>MOT Testing Accrington,Car Servicing Accrington,Car Repairs Accrington,Cambelt Changes Accrington,Small Van Repairs Accrington,Auto Electrics Accrington,Tyre Fitting Accrington,Tyre Sales Accrington,Tinker Brook Garage,Garage Accrington,</keywords><menu>Home,index.html|Contact Us,contactus.html</menu><body>Welcome to Tinker Brook Garage Ltd&amp;#133;&amp;#133;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;For all your quality car and small van repairs and services come along to Tinker Brook Garage Ltd situated in the heart of Accrington.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We supply all members of the general public and tradesmen with our qualified and trained vehicle services for all various makes and designs of car and work van.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Servicing &amp;#126; Repairs &amp;#126; Cambelt Change &amp;#126; Tyre Fitting &amp;#126; Tyre Sales &amp;#126; Auto Electrics&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;With over 20 years experience in the car repairs and servicing business, we have amassed a genuine number of new and returning clientele in Accrington completely satisfied with our quality services.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We are proud to announce that we have previously completed exceptional work for our local Vauxhall garage. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our services include - &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;MOT Testing&lt;BR&gt;Car Servicing&lt;BR&gt;Car Repairs&lt;BR&gt;Cambelt Changes&lt;BR&gt;Small Van Repairs&lt;BR&gt;Auto Electrics&lt;BR&gt;Tyre Fitting&lt;BR&gt;Tyre Sales&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So if your precious and invaluable car or small van requires our professional and fully qualified servicing and repairs service, we are Tinker Brook Garage situated and operating in Accrington.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please don&amp;#146;t hesitate to get in touch with us for more information on our services and competitive prices through the details provided on our contacts page.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We look forward to hearing from you.  &lt;BR&gt;</body><layout>1</layout><content>form1</content><theme>car-performance3</theme><style>1</style><domain>tinkerbrookgarage.com</domain><shadowed>False</shadowed><mainsite></mainsite></root>
